<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Application - Interaction Experience on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>/060-application.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Application - Interaction Experience on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/060-application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preparation</title>
      <link>/060-application/10_first.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/060-application/10_first.html</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s get ready   Step One: Go to the top right corner of the Genesys Cloud CX application (either browser or desktop) and toggle the on-queue switch to on. This turns the user&amp;rsquo;s status to on-queue and available for routing interactions in all queues that the user is active in.
  Step Two: You need to do two things to ensure you&amp;rsquo;re ready to start receiving interactions:
Go to the user profile in the top left corner, and verify: (1) you have a phone/endpoint selected (this will typically be webRTC) and (2) hit the activate queues button and ensure you&amp;rsquo;re activated in the queue you created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Interactions</title>
      <link>/060-application/20_second.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/060-application/20_second.html</guid>
      <description>Scenario The purpose of this scenario is to showcase utilization and how we can manage an omnichannel approach.
  If not already on-queue, toggle the on-queue switch so that your status is &amp;ldquo;on-queue.&amp;rdquo; From here, we&amp;rsquo;re going to trigger two interaction types - email, and chat.
  Send an email to the email address domain you created within the Genesys Cloud CX admin panel. If set up appropriately, it will route directly to the &amp;ldquo;G Ride&amp;rdquo; Queue and to your user in the Agent Interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Interaction</title>
      <link>/060-application/30_third.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/060-application/30_third.html</guid>
      <description>Scenario   Call the phone number purchased earlier that&amp;rsquo;s tied to the call flow uploaded. In the IVR, you will hear the prompt and then be routed to queue. If your user is on-queue, the interaction will be routed to you and interrupt the digital interactions.
NOTE: If you&amp;rsquo;re calling from the phone number listed on your user profile, the interaction will not route to you. Please ensure that the ANI you&amp;rsquo;re calling from is separate than the primary voice number listed in GCCX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnichannel Experience</title>
      <link>/060-application/40_fourth.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/060-application/40_fourth.html</guid>
      <description>Manual Outbound Interactions   You now have, at least, two-three interactions connected, and you&amp;rsquo;re learning the basics of an omnichannel experience. We&amp;rsquo;re going to throw one more interaction type into the mix. On the phone call, the customer requests that the contact center agent sends out a text message with specific information, such as a retail address, for them to quickly access.
  To complete this request, you need to go into the interaction pane and next to the conversations heading, there will be a &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; icon next to a human outline.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
